<!--
  ~    Copyright 2018 Fabien Boismoreau
  ~
  ~    Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
  ~    you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
  ~    You may obtain a copy of the License at
  ~
  ~        http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
  ~
  ~    Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
  ~    distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
  ~    WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
  ~    See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
  ~    limitations under the License.
  -->

<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Monterrey Tour Guide</string>

    <!-- Drawer Menu -->
    <string name="restaurants">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="cultures">Cultures</string>
    <string name="entertainments">Entertainments</string>
    <string name="cinemas">Cinemas</string>

    <string name="descriptionImage">descriptive image</string>
    <string name="objectDetailImage">Point of interest view</string>
    <string name="monterreyCity">Monterrey city</string>

    <!-- Cultures places -->
    <string name="cultureTitle1">Metropolitan Cathedral</string>
    <string name="cultureSummary1">This temple located in the old neighborhood of Monterrey is the seat of the Archdiocese of the city. Account with a tower of three bodies and a sober central ship, with hornacinas chapels in the sides and a cupola of octagonal form. The construction dates from the 18th century, although it mixes neoclassical lines with a baroque façade. The chapel of the tabernacle has a beautiful frontal of embossed silver. In the sacristy there is a series of beautiful paintings from the viceregal period and in the presbytery there are colorful murals by Ángel Zárraga Arguelles, painted during the 1940s.</string>

    <string name="cultureTitle2">Ride Santa Lucia</string>
    <string name="cultureSummary2">It is a water channel of 2.5 kilometers in length, which runs parallel to a pedestrian path, in the first quadrant of the city of Monterrey. Because of its length, it is the longest artificial river in Latin America. The walk was inaugurated in 2007 and quickly became one of the great attractions of the city. The canal is navigated by small boats and along the route there are 24 fountains, plazas, works of art, restaurants and other places of interest. Part of the Macroplaza, ending in the Fundidora Park. It was the emblematic work built on the occasion of the Universal Forum of Cultures of 2007, held in Monterrey.</string>

    <string name="cultureTitle3">Macroplaza</string>
    <string name="cultureSummary3">The Grand Plaza or Macroplaza of downtown Monterrey has an area of 400,000 square meters, making it the fifth largest space in the world of its kind. Its emblematic structure is the Faro del Comercio, a long and thin building, 70 meters high, which at night activates a system of green lasers, visible in almost the entire city. It is the main public space of Monterrey and in its surroundings, the colonial buildings make a striking contrast with modern buildings. It has commercial areas, recreation areas and green areas.</string>

    <string name="cultureTitle4">Government Palace Museum</string>
    <string name="cultureSummary4">This museum was inaugurated in 2006 in the government palace and shows the historical, political and administrative evolution of the state of Nuevo León. The beautiful building of almost 100 years old is of classical architecture, with pink quarry wall tiles and a statue of La Victoria crowning the main façade. In the lobby there are stained glass windows of Miguel Hidalgo and Benito Juárez. In its three rooms there is a tour of the main political, social, economic and legal events throughout the history of the city.</string>

    <string name="cultureTitle5">Museum of Mexican History</string>
    <string name="cultureSummary5">This institution, inaugurated in 1994, is part of the most important museum complex in the city, around the Paseo Santa Lucía, in conjunction with the Government Palace Museum and the Museum of the Northeast. The building is modern design, sober and practical in its three levels. In the permanent room, located on the second floor, a sample of the main pre-Hispanic cultures, the viceregal period, the period of Independence, the nineteenth century Mexico and the modern nation is offered. There is also an area dedicated to the nature of the Mexican territory, showing its characteristics and geological and biological diversity.</string>

    <string name="cultureTitle6">Fundidora Park</string>
    <string name="cultureSummary6">Monterrey is one of the Mexican cities with the longest steel tradition and this beautiful park is on the property that was occupied by the Monterrey Iron and Steel Fundidora company for most of the last century. It is qualified as a site museum in the field of industrial archeology. It has a Plaza of the Visionaries, reminiscent of the pioneers of the iron and steel industry in the city, and the Plaza Grúa Portal, which displays the huge and ancient bridge crane that provided services to the Altos Ovens In the squares of the Altos Hornos, the facilities in which the liquid iron that fed the steel mills were manufactured.</string>

    <!-- Restaurants -->
    <string name="restaurantTitle1">Los Generales</string>
    <string name="restaurantSummary1">Los Generales is the ideal restaurant to share a delicious meal in the company of your loved ones. We have the widest and most delicious variety of dishes for all tastes. Enjoy our exquisite buffets in any of our 6 branches, 7 days a week, 365 days a year.</string>

    <string name="restaurantTitle2">Los Cabritos</string>
    <string name="restaurantSummary2">Los Cabritos has always been distinguished for its excellent quality in its dishes, its specialty is the kid to the shepherd. It also has excellent cuts of meat and delicious snacks. Since its beginnings in 1965, the founder Generoso Martínez Garza has always tried to be in the taste of its customers, and that continues to this day. We invite you to come and taste our delicious dishes and variety of wines, enjoy a delicious time with your family, we will welcome you with open arms.</string>

    <string name="restaurantTitle3">Pollo Loco</string>
    <string name="restaurantSummary3">It is prepared and marinated in an exclusive recipe that has been preserved by the family through several generations. It is a mixture of condiments, herbs, spices and fruits that give it, along with the roasting process, that unique flavor. It was the year of 1974 when its founder "Pancho" began to feel the challenge and the possibility of exploiting this old family recipe to prepare "roast chicken", that\'s how on Monday, January 6, 1975, it was inaugurated in the then small village of Guasave, Sinaloa, the first crazy chicken in the world. The first crazy chicken in the world is still in force in Guasave, Sinaloa on Guerrero Avenue, between doctor de la Torre and Corregidora, as a testimony of the corporate vision of "Pancho" that has conquered the Mexican taste and the global taste for consuming a healthy diet . El Pollo Loco began its rapid growth in our country, Morelia, Saltillo, Torreón, Nuevo Laredo, Reynosa, Mexico City, Piedras Negras, Monterrey and its metropolitan area: Guadalupe, San Nicolás, San Pedro, Santa Catarina and Villa de Juárez .</string>

    <!-- Entertainment -->
    <string name="entertainmentTitle1">Plaza Sesamo</string>
    <string name="entertainmentSummary1">Plaza Sésamo is the first theme park in Mexico and was inaugurated in 1995, in an area of ​​10 hectares located in the Fundidora Park, in the heart of Monterrey. The venture has a varied entertainment offer with mechanical attractions, shows and aquatic shows for all ages, creating unique experiences in a fun and safe environment. The park is inhabited by the famous characters of Sesame Street, who will accompany you along your route, while enjoying the multitude of attractions, rides for the family, three theaters with numerous shows that will delight the little ones and all the amusement of its aquatic park, Aquamundo, with wave pools, swimming pools with unusual slides and the magic of Isla Aventura, with its resting area fully equipped, pools of different types, solarium, a large sandpit to play as if you were in the Beach, the Happy River and the most incredible slides. The tour begins with many surprises in Villasésamo, where you can meet Elmo, Abelardo and other friends, as well as having fun in theaters with the shows and enjoying the most delicious food in any of the restaurants. A special attraction is the photo in Abelardo\'s fountain, a topic that you can not ignore. If you like the Sesame Street characters, you can also celebrate your birthday in the park, with free access to the park for all the guests, shows and many surprises. The park looks after the safety of all its visitors, for which it is forbidden to introduce firearms and / or sharp piercing, foggy bulges, skates, skateboards, pets and radio-recorders. In the main entrance there is a surveillance post where the bags and bags are checked, with no exceptions. The park offers some complementary services such as rental of baby strollers, lockers, toilet services and parking fees. It also has a good gastronomic offer. To stay near Sesame Street you have an interesting accommodation offer, with hotels of all prices and categories, located very close to the park, which you can book in packages that include tickets to Sesame Street. At lunchtime, you can choose among the restaurants that the park offers, with a varied menu to savor as a family.</string>

    <!-- cinemas -->
    <string name="cinemaTitle1">Cinépolis</string>
    <string name="cinemaSummary1">On the billboard of Cinépolis Sendero in Monterrey Sendero you will find the schedules of the premiere films. Reserve your movie tickets now!</string>

    <string name="cinemaTitle2">Cinemex</string>
    <string name="cinemaSummary2">Check the billboard and opening hours of Cinemex Escobedo, located in Escobedo, Monterrey and Metropolitan Area. Do not stay without your tickets!</string>

</resources>
